中东 1997年
零号 我是零一阿尔法 我们已控制住猎鹰
Zero, this is Zero One Alpha. We have secured Falcon.
重复一遍 我们已控制住猎鹰
I say again, We have secured Falcon.
我会从一数到十
I will count from one to ten.
你老实把事情交代清楚
Within that you'll tell me what I wanna know.
否则
Otherwise...
你听到十的时候就是你死的时候
the number ten is the last thing you'll hear.
一
One,
二
two,
三
three...
四
four,
五
five,
六
six,
七
seven,
八
eight...
手榴弹 快躲开
Grenade. Get Back.
真主至上
Allahu Akbar.
靠
Shit.
他妈的给忘了
Fucking missed it
我他妈的怎么就没想到呢
How did I fucking miss it...
梅林 让你亲眼看见他牺牲我很抱歉
Merlin, I apologize for putting you in this position.
你把他训练得很好
You trained him well.
詹姆士
James,
你的训练结束
your training is over.
欢迎加入王牌特工
Welcome to Kingsman,
兰斯洛特
Lancelot.
谢谢长官
Sir
我来善后
I'll deal with this mess.
亲自去办
Personally.
伦敦
你丈夫的英勇牺牲不能公诸于世
I very much regret that your
我感到非常抱歉
husband's bravery can't be publicly celebrated.
我希望你能理解
I hope you understand.
我怎么能理解
How can I understand?
你不告诉我到底发生了什么
You won't tell me anything!
我甚至都不知道他为你的队伍效力
I didn't even know he wasn't with his squad.
很抱歉 我能说的只有这么多了
I'm so sorry, I can't say more.
我想把这枚英勇勋章送给你
I would like to present you with this medal of valor.
如果你仔细看 背面是一串电话号码
If you look closely on the back, there's a number.
为了表达我们更为实际性的感激
And as a more concrete gesture of our gratitude,
我们想给你提供一次
we'd like to offer you a...
可以说是帮助吧
Let's call it a favor.
怎么用完全取决于你
The nature of it is your choice.
只要告诉电话接线员 牛津胜于布洛克
Just tell the operator: "Oxford's, not Brogue's".
我就知道是你打来的了
And then I'll know it's you.
我不需要你的帮助
I don't want your help.
我只想要我丈夫回来
I want my husband back.
小家伙 你叫什么名字
What's your name, young man?
艾格西
Eggsy.
你好啊 艾格西
Hello, Eggsy.
能给我看看吗
Can I see that?
你好好保管这个 艾格西
You take care of this, Eggsy.
好吗
All right?
也好好照顾你妈妈
And take care of your mom too.
阿根廷 17年后
很抱歉 阿诺德教授 马上就好了
So sorry, Professor Arnold. Just a tiny bit more.
哦 去你的 给个痛快吧
Oh for god's sakes, just strip it off.
上级给出了严格指令 我不能伤害你
I am under very strict instructions not to hurt you.
听着 你们搞错了
Look, you've made a mistake.
我只是个大学讲师 我没钱
I am university lecturer. I've got no money.
这事儿跟钱无关
This isn't about money.
我们老板只是想跟你聊聊
Our boss just wants to just talk to you.
所以我要安心了吗
Am I meant to find that reassuring?
他很快就会过来跟你解释清楚的
He'll be here soon. He'll explain.
要喝点威士忌吗
Do you like whiskey?
瑞德 倒一杯62年的达尔摩
Red, get a '62 Dalmore.
不错
Hhmm...
说实话 这酒很赞
Honestly, this whiskey is amazing.
喝了你就知道了
You will shit.
我要说我是来借一杯糖的 会太过分吗
I suppose asking to borrow a cup of sugar is a step too far?
阿诺德教授
Professor Arnold,
我是来带你回家的
I'm here to take you home.
嗯 1962年的达尔摩
Hmm... 1962 Dalmore.
浪费一滴都是罪过啊
It would be a sin to spill any.
你不觉得吗
Don't you think?
你能拿一下吗
Can you hold these?
有劳了
Please.
谢谢
Thank you.
都收拾好了
Everything is clean.
我喜爱的欢迎方式
My kind of welcome.
我不喜欢暴力
No stomach for violence.
绝不夸张
I mean, literally.
只要看到一滴血 我就
I see one drop of blood, that is me..
完了
Done.
我就会
I am like...
狂吐不止
projectile.
听着 我很抱歉
Listen, I'm so sorry...
让你目睹了这般血腥场面
you had to witness all this unpleasantness.
只因这位不速之客
Due to our uninvited guest.
但是我保证
But I promise you,
等我查出来他究竟为谁效力之时
By the time I find out who he works for...
我们会成为最好的朋友的
you and I will be the best of friends.
在店门口停车 谢谢
To the shop, please.
萨维尔街
威斯敏斯特市
皇家绅士
先生 亚瑟在餐厅
Arthur is in the dining room, sir.
亚瑟
Arthur.
加拉哈德
Galahad.
大家都在想我们这次
The others were beginning to
是不是要致敬两次了
wonder if we were going to have a double toast.
各位 我很欣慰 距离我们上次开这瓶酒
Gentlemen, I am thankful to say that it's been 17 years...
已经过去十七年了
since we last had occasion to use this decanter.
兰斯洛特是一位杰出的特工 也是一位真正的皇家绅士
Lancelot was an outstanding agent and a true Kingsman.
他会被历史所铭记的
He will be sorely missed.
敬兰斯洛特
To Lancelot.
To Lancelot
我打算从明天起
I intend to start the selection
开始挑选兰斯洛特的接班人
process for Lancelot's replacement tomorrow.
希望你们每人推选一名候选人
I want each of you to propose a candidate
并上报英国总部
and have them report to UK HQ
不得迟于格林威治时间晚上九点
No later than 9 p.M. GMT.
谢谢
Thank you.
梅林
Merlin.
请进
Come in.
兰斯洛特生前一直在调查一帮
Lancelot was investigating a group of mercenaries
进行生化武器实验的雇佣兵
who were experimenting with biological weaponry.
各位请戴上眼镜
Glasses, gentlemen. Please.
2012年 乌干达 合成卡西酮
Uganda, 2012. Synthetic Cathinone.
污染了陆军基地的供给水源
You put it in the water supply of a guerrilla army base.
引发了愤怒和自相残杀 导致了大量伤亡
Rage, cannibalism. Multiple fatalities.
2013年 车臣
Chechnya, 2013.
叛乱分子互相反目
Insurgents turned on one another.
显然是雇佣兵干的
Indisputable, the work of our
但没发现任何化学物质
mercenaries but no trace of any chemicals of any kind.
所以兰斯洛特是怎么死的
So what happened to Lancelot?
他追踪到他们窝藏在阿根廷的这所房子里
He tracked them to this property in Argentina.
在监视他们的过程中
And while he had them under surveillance,
他发现了一起绑架案
he became aware that they had effected a kidnapping.
所以他执行了一次独立营救 结果失败了
So he executed a solo rescue mission... which failed.
这是他最后传出的信息
This is his last transmission:
绑架案受害者是詹姆士·阿诺德教授
▄
-他是谁 -某位气候变化末日论者
- Who is he? - Some climate change doomsayer.
推广盖亚论
Expounded something called Gaia
认为世界能自愈 诸如此类
theory about the world healing itself or some such.
但奇怪的是 他并没有失踪
But what's curious, is he's not actually missing.
这就是阿诺德教授
This is Professor Arnold.
今天早上现身帝国理工学院
At Imperial College, this morning.
你们来处理此事 还有别忘了候选人的事
It's all yours. And don't forget your membership proposal.
这次尽量找个更为适合的候选人
Try picking a more suitable candidate this time.
十七年了
17 years
你还是无法理解
and still evolving with the
与时俱进这个概念吗
times remains an entirely foreign concept to you.
是不是需要我提醒你
Need I remind you, I wouldn't
如果没有那个年轻人 我不可能活到现在
be here if it weren't for that young man.
他完全具备成为王牌特工的潜质
He was as much Kingsman material as any of them.
甚至更优秀
More so.
但确切来说 他并没成为我们的一员 不是吗
But he wasn't exactly one of us, was he?
面对现实吧 加拉哈德 你的小实验失败了
Let's face it, Galahad. Your little experiment failed.
恕我直言 亚瑟 你是个势利小人
With respect, Arthur, you're a snob.
何出此言
With respect?
世界在变化
The world is changing.
贵族们都遗传了小下巴是有原因的
There's a reason why aristocrats developed weak chins.
艾格西
Eggsy?
艾格西 过来一下
Eggsy, come here.
-你有卷烟纸 宝贝儿 -没有
- Got any whistler, babe? - No.
不如你帮你妈妈
Why don't you do your mamma a favor,
下楼买一些回来吧
Go down to the shop and get some.
-要去你自己去 -噢
- Get 'em yourself. - Oh, What I
不是告诉过你 不要用这种语气跟迪安说话吗
have said to you about speaking to Dean like that?
你们不嫌挤吗 不如让迪安的贵宾犬去买啊
Three's a crowd, isn't it Why don't Dean's poodle go?
这样吧
I tell you what,
这钱你拿去买
Why don't you take this and
其余的钱给你随便花
get the stuff and get yourself some sweets?
你走之后 我会让你妈妈看看
And while you're gone, we'll
三是一个多么美好的数字
show your mother how three can be good a company.
谢了宝贝儿
Thanks babe.
过来
Come here.
给你这个
Here we go.
好些了吗
Is it better?
如果迪安对你妈妈不好 她为什么不离开他
If Dean treat your mum's so bad, why doesn't she leave him?
缺乏自尊心
Low self-esteem.
那就是她的问题了
That's her problem.
去你的 她怎么会缺乏自尊心
Fuck off, why would she have low self-esteem?
艾格西的妈妈跟谁都合得来
Eggsy mum's a world fit.
-无意冒犯 -没事
- No offense pal. - It's all right.
总有一天我要
- One of these days I'm
-撕烂他的脸 -你是脑残吗
gonna smash his face in. - Are you mental, cuz?
他只会让他那些小弟对付你
He'll just get that lot
然后假装他什么事
to do you and then pretend he knew nothing
都不知道
about it.
别以为仗着我们老大在泡艾格西他妈
Oy, you think you can chat shit about us and we wont do nothing,
我们就会任由你们说闲话
just because our governor bangin' Eggsy's mum?
就仗着怎么了
Pretty much, yeah.
别这样 我们走吧 不值得
Leave it, let's just go, man. It's not worth it.
这里不欢迎你们几个了
You boys have outstayed your welcome.
滚
Leave.
怎么
What?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry about that bruh.
这才对嘛 小杂种
Yeah... muck.
我们不跟他们一般见识
They weren't fucking worth it, Boys.
好冷啊 为什么我们要走路呢
It's freezing. Why are we walking?
你偷了他的车钥匙
- You jacked his fucking car keys,
没错 我们现在就顺走他的车
bruh? - Yeah, now we're gonna nick his car.
我勒个去
Fucking shit.
等一下
Hold on boys.
嘿 这他妈是我的车
Hey, That's my fucking car.
艾格西
Oi, Oi, Eggsy.
我告诉你 你摊上大事儿了
I swear, you're in fucking trouble.
全速前进吧 艾格西
Floor it, Eggsy.
嘿 迪安 是我
Hey yeah Dean, look it's me.
他妈的 艾格西刚偷了我的车
Eggsy just stole my fucking car.
我刚从酒吧出来 他刚才当着我的面
I've come out of the pub, He's done 15
原地转车十五圈 然后把我的车开走了
about donuts on my fucking face and then he's drove off.
不 不能忍 他不尊重我就是不尊重你
No, I cant, He's disrespecting me and so he's disrespecting you.
混蛋
Thickie.
狐狸不是什么好东西 你就应该直接碾过去的
Foxes are vermin, cuz. You should've driven it over.
我应该要做的事情太多了
I should've done a lot of things.
这事交给我 你们下车吧
I'll sort this, get out of the car.
他妈的快下车
Get out of the fucking car.
艾格西 窃贼之间可没什么盗亦有道
Eggsy, there is no such thing as honor among thieves.
现在你可以告诉我
Now you can start giving
你的同伙是哪些人了
me some names of the boys you were with...
要不然你就一个人蹲监狱
Or you go down.
这取决于你
It's up to you.
我想行使打电话的权利
I want to exercise my right to a phone call.
好吧 我希望是打给你妈妈
Well, I hope it's to your mom...
告诉她你得
to tell her that you're
迟到十八个月才能回家吃饭了
gonna to be 18 months late for your dinner.
客户投诉中心 请问您需要什么帮助
Customer complaints. How may I help you?
我叫艾格西·恩维 不对 是加里·恩维
My name's Eggsy Unwin. Sorry, Gary Unwin.
我犯了点事儿 现在在城区警察局
And I'm up shit creek, I'm in an urban police station and
我妈说需要帮助时就打这个电话
my mom said to call this number if ever I needed help...
我很抱歉 先生 你打错了
I'm sorry, sir. Wrong number.
等等 等等
Wait, wait
牛津胜于布洛克
Oxford's not Brogue's?
您的投诉已被受理
Your complaint has been duly noted,
希望我们不会失去您这位忠实的客户
and we hope that we've not lost you as a loyal customer.
怎么了
Yeah...
操 什么
Shit, What?
好 我明白
Yes, I totally understand.
艾格西
Eggsy
想搭个便车回家吗
Would you like a lift home?
你是哪位
Who are you?
保你出警察局的人
The man who got you released.
你还没回答我的问题
That ain't an answer.
就不能表示一下感激之情吗
A little gratitude would be nice.
我叫哈利·哈特
My name is Harry Hart.
是我给你的那枚勋章
And I gave you that medal.
你父亲救过我的命
Your father saved my life.
你做裁缝之前是当兵的吗
So before you was a tailor, were you in the army?
军官什么的
Like an officer?
不算是
Not quite.
你在哪服役 伊拉克还是
So where was you posted, Iraq or something?
抱歉 艾格西 这是机密
Sorry, Eggsy. Classified.
但我爸爸救过你 对吧
But my dad saved your life, yeah?
你父亲去世那天
The day your father died,
确实是我疏忽了
I missed something.
倘若不是他的勇气
And if it weren't for his courage, my mistake
我的失误会导致在场所有人的身亡
would have cost the lives of every man present.
我欠他太多
So I owe him.
你父亲是个勇敢的人
Your father was a brave man.
是个好人
A good man.
我看了你的档案
And having read your files, I'd think
我觉得他会对你的人生选择非常失望
he'd be bitterly disappointed in the choices you've made.
别用这种口吻跟我说话
You can't talk to me like that.
高智商 从小学就表现优异
Huge IQ, great performance in primary school.
后来却不务正业
And it all went tits up.
毒品 小偷小摸 无所事事
Drugs, petty crime, never had a job.
你觉得工作有那么好找吗
Do you think there's a lot of jobs going around here?
这也解释不了你为何要放弃自己爱好
Doesn't explain why you gave up your hobbies.
连续两年 地区十岁以下组别的
First prize, regional under tens' gymnastics
体操冠军
Two years in a row. Your
你的教练视你为奥运队的料
coach had you pegged as Olympic team material.
是啊 但跟我继父这样的人一起生活
Yeah and when you grow up around someone like my
刷新三观都是分分钟的事
step-dad, you pick up new hobbies pretty quick.
是啊是啊 永远都是别人的错
Ah of course, always someone else's fault.
那你从海军陆战队退出该怪谁
And who's to blame you for quitting the Marines?
你在训练中途就退出了
You were halfway through training,
你表现优异 但你放弃了
doing brilliantly, but you gave up.
因为我妈变得有点神经质
Because my mum went mental.
生怕像失去我爸那样失去了我
Banging on about losing me as well as my dad.
我们不必为了你们这样的势利小人当炮灰
Then we wouldn't be cannon fodder for snobs like
你们在象牙塔里对我这种人指手画脚
you, judging people like me from your ivory towers.
却根本不考虑我们为何会这么做
With no thought about why we do what we do.
我们没有太多的选择 你知道吗
We ain't got much choice, you get me?
如果我们也含着金钥匙出生
And if we was born with the same silver spoon up our arses...
就算不比你们优秀 我们也至少过得
we would do just as well as you,
和你们一样好
if not better.
你他妈的怎么在这儿 胆儿肥了啊
What the fuck you doing here? You taking a piss?
这些人也是距离成功
Some more examples of young
只差嘴里的一把金钥匙吗
men who simply need a silver suppository?
不 他们是例外 走吧
Ya, they are exceptions. Come on.
才不 我们还没喝完呢
Nonsense, we haven't finished our drinks.
你偷了他的车后 迪安说以后对你不需要客气
After you nicked his car, Dean says you're a
你妈现在说什么都不管用了
fair guy I don't give a shit what your mum says.
听着 孩子们
Listen, boys.
我今天过得相当不快
I've had a rather emotional day,
不管你们跟艾格西有什么过节
so whatever your beef with Eggsy is,
我也知道他确实闯了不少祸
and I'm sure it's well founded...
但如果能让我们清静一会儿
I would appreciate it
待我喝完这杯爱尔兰啤酒
enormously if you could just leave us in peace...
我将不胜感激
until I finish this lovely pint of Guinness.
你应该赶紧离开这儿
You should get out of the way,
老爷爷 不然你会受重伤的
Granddaddy. Or you'll get hurt a lot.
他没开玩笑 你快走
He ain't joking, you should go.
借过
Excuse me.
如果你要另外找多一个男妓
If you're looking for another rent boy,
史密斯街的拐角处有不少呢
they're on the corner of Smith's Street.
不知礼
Manners...
无以
maketh...
立也
man.
知道这句话是什么意思吗
Do you know what that means?
那就容我来给你上一课吧
Then let me teach you a lesson.
你们是打算站那儿一整天吗
Are we going to stand around here all day,
还是要痛痛快快打一架
or are we going to fight?
去你的 去你的
You fucking... You fucking...
昏昏倒地
"Stun"
一忘皆空
Amnesia
很抱歉让你看到这些
Sorry about that.
我要发泄一下才行
Needed to let off a little steam.
我听说一个朋友昨天去世了
Heard, yesterday a friend of mine died.
其实 他也认识你的父亲
He knew your father too, actually.
真的很抱歉 艾格西
I do apologise, Eggsy.
我不应该在你面前大打出手
I should not have done this in front of you.
不 求你了 我一个字也不会说什么 我发誓
No. Please.. I won't say nothing, I swear.
我最在行的就是守口如瓶了
If there is one thing I can do, it's keep my mouth shut.
你不会和任何人说吗
- You won't tell a soul?
我发誓 我从来不骗人
- I swear, I've never crossed anyone out.
-你保证吗 -以我的生命起誓
Is that a promise? - On my life.
非常感谢 艾格西
Much appreciated, Eggsy.
你刚刚说的势利小人那些都很有道理
You're right about the snobs.
但是 也会有例外的
But there too, there are exceptions.
希望你一切顺利
Best of luck with everything.
下面播报名人新闻 昨晚
In celebrity news, The Richmond
瓦丁伦电影首映会
由里奇蒙·瓦伦丁投资拍摄的电影在好莱坞首次公演
Valentine movie premiered in Hollywood, last night.
这部电影讲述了互联网亿万富翁发家的传奇故事
The story of the Internet billionaire's rise to power
将会是各大颁奖盛典的热门之选
is expected to be this award season's hot ticket.
值得关注的是 红毯上缺少了伊基·阿塞莉娅的身影
One notable absence from the red carpet was
关注失踪歌手
她现在仍然不知所踪
Iggy Azalea, still missing three days after...
艾格西 快跑 他要
Eggsy, just go. Please because he's gonna...
-求求你不要伤害他 -滚开
- Please don't hurt him. - Fuck off!
他妈的给我闭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
和你一起在酒吧里的人是谁
Who was with you in that fucking pub?
告诉我那个老头的名字
- I want to know the name of
我没跟任何人在一起
the geezer you was with. - I was not with anyone.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're on about.
你他妈的快告诉我他的名字
Fucking tell me his name.
我不知道你他妈的在说什么
I don't know what you're fucking on about.
你给我听好了
You listen to me, I want to
我要知道和你一起在酒吧里的人是谁 听明白了吗
know who you was with in that pub. You Understand?
我要知道他叫什么名字
I want to know his fucking name.
我不知道你他妈的在说什么
I don't know what you're fucking on about.
给我滚开
Fuck off.
我现在就可以杀了你
I could kill you right now
而且没有任何人会知道
and no one in the the world will know it.
我知道
But I would.
我有足够的证据起诉你
I have enough evidence on your activities to
足以让你下半辈子都待在监狱里
have you locked up for the rest of your life.
迪安·安东尼·贝克先生
Mister Dean Anthony Baker.
我劝你放开这个男孩
So I suggest you leave the boy alone.
不然我就只好
Or I shall be forced to
把这些证据送到相关部门了
deliver it to the appropriate authorities.
艾格西 到我和你说过的裁缝店见我
Eggsy, meet me at the tailor's I told you about.
这他妈的是怎么回事
What the fuck's going on here?
艾格西 你这该死的蛆虫
Eggsy, you fucking maggot...
这次我们一定要抓住他
Here's we gotta arrest him.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey... hey... hey
给我过来
Come here.
你个混蛋
You wanker!
我很快就会抓到你的
I'll have you soon.
皇家绅士
我从没见过裁缝
I've never met a tailor before.
但我知道你肯定不是
But I know you ain't one.
跟我来
Come with me.
进来吧
Come on here.
你看见了什么
What do you see?
一个想知道这到底是怎么回事的人
Someone who wants to know what the fuck is going on.
我看见了一个有潜力的年轻人
I see a young man with potential.
一个忠诚的年轻人
A young man who is loyal.
一个可以服从命令
Who can do as he is asked,
想要在有生之年出人头地的人
and who wants to do something good with his life.
你看过《运转乾坤》这部电影吗
Did you see the film "Trading Places"?
没有
No
那《尼基塔》呢
How about "Nikita"?
《风月俏佳人》呢
"Pretty Woman"?
好吧
All right.
我想说的是 出身平凡是对你造成了一定影响
My point is, the lack of a silver spoon has set you
但你并不需要一直纠结于此
on a certain path, but you needn't stay on it.
如果你愿意适应并且学习 你就可以彻底改变自己的命运
If you're prepare to adapt and learn, you can transform.
喔 像《窈窕淑女》那样吗
Oh, like in "My Fair Lady"?
我就知道你总是能给我带来惊喜
I know you're full of surprises.
对 就是像《窈窕淑女》那样
Yes, like "My Fair Lady"
只不过这次
Only in this case, I am
我是在给你一个做皇家绅士的机会
offering you the opportunity to become a Kingsman.
一个裁缝吗
A tailor?
一个王牌特工
A Kingsman agent.
-就好像间谍一样吗 -差不多吧
- Like a spy? - Of sorts.
有兴趣吗
Interested?
我有什么可犹豫的呢
You think I've got anything to lose?
1849年以来 皇家绅士裁缝店
Since 1849, Kingsman Tailors
就为世界上最具权势的人缝衣做衫
have clothed the world's most powerful individuals.
1919年 第一次世界大战的时候
In 1919, a great number
许多人都失去了他们的继承人
of them had lost their heirs to World War 1.
这就意味着大量的遗产没有人继承
That meant a lot of money going un-inherited.
许多有权势的人
And a lot of powerful men
都想要维护和平和保护世界
with a desire to preserve peace and protect life.
我们的创始人意识到他们可以
Our founders realized that they could channel
运用这些财富和影响力做更有益的事情
that wealth and influence for a greater good.
于是就创立了王牌特工学院
And so began our adventure.
一家独立的国际性情报机构
An independent international intelligence agency
拥有最高自由裁量权
operating at the highest level of discretion.
没有政治牵绊和官僚主义
Without the politics and bureaucracy...
因为那正是破坏政府间谍组织凝聚力的元凶
that undermine the integrity of government run spy organizations.
一套西装就好比现代绅士的盔甲
A suit is the modern gentleman's armor.
而王牌特工就是新一代的骑士
And the Kingsman agents are the new knights.
-这个鬼东西有多深 -深到足够隐蔽
- How deep does this fucking thing go? - Deep enough.
靠 我们迟到了
Shit. We're late.
你的父亲之前也是这样一副表情
Your father had the same look on his face.
我也是
As did I.
来吧
Come on.
-加拉哈德 -我的代号
- Galahad. - My code name.
你又迟到了 先生
Late again, sir.
祝你好运
Good Luck.
进去吧
In you go.
全体集合
Fall in.
女士们先生们 我是梅林
Ladies and gentlemen, my name is Merlin.
你们即将面临的可能是
You are about to embark on what is probably the
世界上最危险的求职面试
most dangerous job interview in the world.
你们当中只有一个人会成为下一个兰斯洛特
One of you and only one of you will become the next Lancelot.
有没有人可以告诉我这个是什么
Can anybody tell me what this is?
-装尸袋 先生 -正确
- A body bag, sir. - Correct.
-查理 是吗 -是的 先生
- Charlie, isn't it? - Yes, sir.
你们每个人马上都会分到一个装尸袋
In a moment, you will each collect a body bag.
你们要在上面写上你们的名字
You will write your name on that bag.
以及你亲人的详细信息
You will write the details of your next of kin. On that bag.
这意味着你们都知道
This represents your acknowledgment of
接下来你们将会面对怎样的风险
the risks that you are about to face...
同时你们也同意会对此严格保密
as well as your agreement to strict
如果不小心泄露出去
confidentiality, which incidentally if you break...
你和你的亲人都会裹上那个袋子
will result in you and your next of kin being in that bag.
明白了吗
Is that understood?
很好
Excellent.
解散
Fall out.
洛克仙妮 但
Roxanne. But..
叫我洛克茜就好了
Call me Roxy.
-我是艾格西 -艾基吗
- I am Eggsy. - Eggy?
不 是艾格西
No, Eggsy
艾基 他们是在哪里找到你的
Eggy... and where did they dig you up?
你明知道我们是不能一起讨论举荐人的
You know we are not allowed to discuss who proposed us.
不至于这么凶吧
No need to bite his head off.
查理只是想闲聊一下 对吧查理
Charlie's only making conversation, right Charlie?
我是迪格比
I'm Digby.
迪格比
Digby.
艾基 这是
Eggy, this is
鲁弗斯
Rufus.
鲁弗斯 艾基
Rufus, Eggy.
所以艾基 你是来自牛津还是剑桥
So Eggy, are you Oxford or Cambridge?
都不是
Neither.
圣安德鲁斯大学 杜伦大学吗
St. Andrews? Durham?
噢 等等 我们好像见过
Oh wait, I think we may have met.
你之前是不是在温彻斯特服务站的麦当劳端过盘子啊
Did you serve me at the McDonalds in Winchester Service Station?
没有
No.
但如果有的话 我一定会给你的汉堡里加料的
But if I had, I give you an extra helping of secret sauce.
这一听就是圣安德鲁斯的人
It's definitely St. Andrews.
-不要理他们 -你需要笔吗
- Just ignore them. - Do you need a pen?
谢谢
Cheers.
阿米莉娅 是吗
- Amelia, isn't it?
-阿米莉娅 -艾格西
- Amelia, - Eggsy
嗨 艾格西
Hi Eggsy!
千万不要搭理那些家伙
Don't take any notice of those guys.
我也是这么跟他说的
That's what I told him.
这只是恐吓战术
It's just scare tactics.
典型的军队伎俩
Classic army technique.
没人会死的
No one's gonna die.
真遗憾
Shame.
很好 所以你不知道 中央情报局也不知道
Great, so you don't know, the CIA don't know.
就没有人知道这家伙是谁吗
Nobody knows who this guy is?
好吧
Fine.
说真的 没关系的
Seriously, it's fine.
好吧 也不是真的没关系
Well, it's not really fine but
这并不是我来这儿的原因
it's not why I'm here.
该死的 你知道我是谁吧
Hell man, you know me?
钱对我而言从来不是问题
Money's not my issue.
我完全可以直接从麻省理工退休
I could have retired straight out of MIT, fucked off
到某个小岛上享受天伦 让公司自己运行
to some island and let the business run itself.
没有人让我拯救地球
Nobody told me to try and save the planet.
但我想
I wanted to.
气候变化研究 游说
Climate change research, lobbying,
多年的研究 数十亿美元的投入
years of studying, billions of dollars.
可你知道我为什么退出了吗
And you know why I quit?
因为到现在为止 这个星球仍是一团糟
Because the last time I checked, the planet was still fucked.
所以 我顿悟了
Hence, my epiphany.
钱并不能解决这个问题
Money won't solve this.
那些傻瓜政客
Those idiots who call themselves politicians,
只会逃避现实
they bury their heads in the sand...
只知道不停地改选
and stood for nothing but re-election.
所以过去的两年里 我一直在寻找一个可行的解决办法
So I spent the last two years trying to find a real solution.
我真的找到了
And I found it.
现在 如果你真的想让世界变得更好
Now, If you really want to make the world a better place...
我劝你他妈的给我听好了
I suggest you open your fucking ears
因为我现在就打算和你好好说说
because I'm about to tell it to you.
继续说 瓦伦丁先生
Go on, Mr. Valentine.
洗耳恭听
I'm still listening.
只要你同意我的所有条款
As long as you agree to all my terms.
不要害怕 听我的 冷静
No one panic. Listen to me. Stay calm.
-用通气管 -为什么
- Use snorkels. - Use snorkels?
-花洒 -花洒?
- Shower heads. - Shower heads?
她说得对 走 快走
She's right. Go. Fucking go.
为什么不试试把门打开呢
And what about pulling the fucking door?
恭喜
Congratulations
你们完成了第一个任务
on completing your first task.
查理 罗克茜 做得好
Charlie, Roxy, well done.
那些还不知道原因的人 我来告诉你们
For those who 're still confused
如果你把通气管插入马桶的U形部分
If you get a breathing tube run the U-bend of
你就拥有了取之不尽的空气供给
a toilet, you have an unlimited air supply.
简单的物理原理 值得牢记
Simple physics. Worth remembering.
艾格西
Eggsy,
很好 能发现这是个双向镜
Well done for spotting that was a two-way mirror.
他之前可能看过很多吧[警局里面都是用这种镜子]
He is probably seen enough of 'em.
你们都把傻笑给我收起来
Yeah you can all wipe those smirks off your faces.
因为在我眼里
Because as far as I am concerned,
你们每一个人都不合格
every single one of you has failed.
你们都忘记了最重要的事情
You all forgot the most important thing:
团队合作
Teamwork.
这就是所谓的经典军队伎俩啊
So much for classic army technique.
35,
5.
就是这样
That's it.
你好
Hello?
有什么可以帮到你的吗
Can I help you?
嗯 我有个关于人类起源的问题
Yes, I have a question about anthropogenic force.
真的吗 这其实是很有趣的
Really? Well, it's actually quite fascinating.
我的同事为了救你而死
My colleague died trying to rescue you.
你肯定已经见识过他是多么的训练有素了
And I'm sure you saw how well-trained he was.
所以我希望你能告诉我
So I suggest you tell me
是谁绑架了你 而他们为什么又放了你
who kidnapped you and why they let you go.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about...
我不能说 这是
I can not say, it was...
噢 拜托 我都还没有怎么用力呢 怎么可以
Oh for god's sake, I barely touched you. How man are...
植入芯片已激活
我去他的 不管他是谁 我都要
Fuck that guy, whoever he is, I'm gonna...
他害我杀了阿诺德教授
He made me kill Professor Arnold.
惹人爱的阿诺德教授
Goddamn loved Professor Arnold.
好消息是
Well the good news is
我们知道应急和监察系统起作用了
we know the emergency and surveillance systems work.
你知道什么是坏消息吗
You know what is not good news?
“我的同事死了”
"My colleague died."
他就是这么说的
That's what he said.
这可是一个组织 而且他们在找我们
This is an organization and they are all over us.
不管你和谁说
Whoever you spoke to...
我告诉过你 我跟苏联国家安全委员会
I told you, I am in contact with the KGB,
军情六处 摩萨德 北京都联系过了
MI6, Mossad and Beijing.
他们都坚称他不是他们的人
They all insist he wasn't one of theirs.
北京
Beijing.
中国特务机关就不能
So freaky how there's no
取个别的名字吗 真是可怕
recognizable name for the Chinese Secret Service.
这样你们也好意思说是秘密机关吗
Now that's what you call a secret, right?
你知道吗
You know what?
管他的 我们要加快进度了
Fuck it. We need to speed things up.
提前召开产品发布会
Bring the product release forward.
可是生产只进行到一半
They are only halfway into production.
加快进度会花掉一大笔钱的
Speeding it will cost a fortune.
你觉得我会在意这点钱吗 快点去做就是了
Do I look like I give a fuck? Just get it done..
正如你们昨晚所学到的
As some of you will have learned last night:
在这里 团队合作最重要的
Teamwork is paramount here at Kingsman.
我们要提高你们的技能 挑战你们的极限
We are here to enhance your skills, test you to limits.
所以你们现在要选一只狗
Which is why you're gonna pick a puppy.
你们去到哪里 狗就要跟到哪里
Wherever you go, your dog goes.
你们要爱护它 训练它
You will care for it, you will teach it.
它们完成训练之时 也会是你们完成训练之日
And by the time they are fully trained, so will you be.
这话是针对那些最终留下来的人
Those of you who are still here, that is.
明白了吗
Do you understand?
来选你们的狗吧
Choose your puppy.
贵宾犬吗
A poodle?
什么啊
What?
它们是猎犬
They are gun dogs.
最古老的工作犬种
Oldest working breed.
易于训练
Easy to train.
哈巴狗吗
A pug?
这不是斗牛犬吗
It's a bulldog, isn't it?
它会慢慢长大的 对吧
It would get bigger though, wouldn't it?
我靠
Ssshhhit
核磁共振结果显示他没有脑震荡
His MRI shows no signs of concussion.
也没有脑部创伤
No direct brain trauma at all.
他还要多久才会醒过来
How much longer can he be out?
这是很重要的问题
That's the million-dollar question.
我们都不知道他受到了什么的袭击
We don't know what he was exposed to in there.
哈里拍到的影片呢
What about Harry's footage?
没有发送到他的终端接收器吗
It didn't stream to his home terminal?
加密了 无法破解
Encrypted and uncrackable.
等他醒过来的时候 你可能
If and when he comes round, you might wanna have
得问一下他的密码是什么
a word with him about sharing his password.
他会没事的吧
Is he gonna be alright?
我们要有耐心 艾格西
We need to have patience, Eggsy.
还是有希望的 好吗
But there is hope. Okay?
如果我是你 我就会专心训练
If I were you, I'd concentrate on your training.
通过测试 让他骄傲
Make it through the test, make him proud.
来啊 JB 来啊
Come on, J. B. Come on.
你不要害我只能拿最后一名啊
I am not coming last cause of you.
JB 我会杀了你 该死的 我真的会杀了你的
J. B, I'll shoot you, goddamn. I'll fucking shoot you.
梅林说我们不可以抱着你
Merlin said we're not allowed to hold you.
管他的
Bollocks.
淹水了
Water.
来打一架吧
Come on then.
艾格西 算了吧
Eggsy, you forget it.
哎呀怎么啦 连个玩笑都开不起吗
Oh what's wrong mate, can't take a joke?
说真的 你会被赶出去的 太不值了
Seriously, you'll get turned out and it's just not worth it.
也许我不在意被赶出去呢
Maybe I don't give a fuck about getting kicked out.
真的吗 那来吧 你个小东西
Really? Come on, you player.
查理 滚开
Charlie, fuck off.
对 走吧 走得远远的
Yeah, go on, walk away.
白痴
Dickhead.
抱抱 JB
Come on, J. B.
没事了
It's all right.
你们有一个小时的时间来完成测试
You have exactly one hour to complete the test.
现在开始
Starting now.
-新目标 八百米处 -简直难以相信 你还在这里
- New target. 800 meters. - It's unbelievable. You're still here.
就像赶也赶不走的冤魂缠身
Lingering on like some big steaming shit that just won't flush.
收到
Roger that.
目标已识别 不如你还是闭嘴吧
Target identified. And how about you shut the fuck up.
正面差别待遇
Positive discrimination.
这是值得的
It's worth it.
就好像那些因为妈妈是独腿同性恋者
Like those fucking steak cooks who go down seaways
就能走海上航道的厨师一样
because their mum's a one-legged lesbian.
你一点都不了解我的成绩
You don't know fuck-all about my grades.
噢 原谅我 我肯定你是受过高等教育的
Oh forgive me. I'm sure you're highly educated.
准备好了就开火
Fire when ready.
这个正面差别待遇如何
How's that for positive discrimination?
我很感谢你们的倾听
I wanna thank you both for listening.
我真的真的很感激你不远万里来到这里
And I really, really appreciate your traveling all this way,
尊敬的公主殿下
Your Royal Highness.
还有你 首相大人
And you too, Prime Minister.
我觉得这主意真是好极了
I think this is quite brilliant.
这真的是太棒了
It is absolutely brilliant.
你一定是疯了
You are completely crazy.
抱歉 尊敬的公主殿下
I'm sorry, Your Royal Highness...
但是想要斯堪的纳维亚重回正轨
but you got a big role to play...
你可是起着很重要的作用呢
in getting the Scandinavian region back on track.
你很受欢迎 能鼓舞人们
You're popular, inspirational and
最重要的是能够煽动人心
you have the power to galvanize the people.
现在不管你同不同意
Now whether you're on board or not...
我都必须要
I am going to have to insist
带你到一个能确保你安全的地方
on getting you somewhere I can ensure your safety.
你怎么看 首相大人
How about you, Prime Minister?
要加入我们吗
You in or out?
当然 我认为是时候让
Well, I think it's about time that
一个政治家做点
a politician did something that...
能够真正改变世界的事情了
actually made a difference.
说的太对了
Too true.
把她带走
Take her away.
喝一杯吗
Drink?
好啊
Why not?
等等 救救我
Wait, help me.
别担心 我们不会伤害她的
Do not worry. No harm will come to the princess.
反正我是共和党人 我不介意
Well I'm Republican anyway, so it really doesn't matter.
放开公主
Release the princess.
好啦 搞定了
Okay, you're done.
不会太痛吧
Not too bad, right?
几乎没有感觉
I hardly felt a thing.
欢迎加入我们
Welcome aboard.
我很荣幸
The pleasure is all mine.
不知道敲门吗
Ever heard of knocking?
只有在踩点抢劫的时候我才会敲门
Only when I'm casing a place to rob.
阿米莉娅说你想要见我
Amelia said you wanted to see me.
希望JB和你的训练都很顺利
Hope J. B.'s training is going as well as yours is.
坐下
Sit.
恭喜你成为最后的六强
Congratulations on making it to the final six candidates.
你的测试结果比我所期待的还要好
Your test results are even better than I could've hoped.
请进
Come in.
艾格西 我要和他私下谈谈
Eggsy, I need to have a private conversation.
你可以出去了
You're dismissed.
不用了 让他待着吧 他会学到点东西的
Nonsense, let him observe. He'd learn a thing or two.
随你吧 看看这个
As you wish. Take a look at this.
我勒个去 那可是他的 哈里
Fucking hell. That's his... harry.
你爆了他的头吗
You blew up his head?
这可有点过了啊 不是吗
It's a bit much, isn't it?
事实上 爆炸来源于他脖子里的植入物
Actually, the explosion was caused by an implant in his neck.
这儿 就在那道伤疤下面
Here. Under that scar.
我的装置有没有追踪到它的引爆信号
Did my hardware pick up the signal that triggered it?
幸运的是 有
Fortunately, yes.
不幸的是 IP地址
Unfortunately, the IP address
追踪到了瓦伦丁名下公司
it traced it to is registered to the Valentine Corporation.
这没什么用啊
It's not much of a lead.
他们在全球有成千上万的员工
They have millions of employees worldwide.
不 里奇蒙·瓦伦丁是个天才
No, Richmond Valentine is a genius.
你们没有看他今天的发布会吗
Did you not see his announcement today?
没有
No.
我们每人每年平均
We each spend on average
花费两千美元在手机和互联网的使用上
$2,000 a year on cellphone and internet usage.
我在这里很荣幸地宣布
It gives me great pleasure to announce,
新的时代即将来临
those days are over.
因为明天 每个男人
As of tomorrow, every man,
女人和孩子都可以得到一张免费的手机卡
woman and child can claim a free SIM card...
适用于任何手机 电脑
compatible with any cellphone, any computer and...
并且可以免费使用我的通讯网络
utilize my communications network for free.
免费通话 免费上网 人人兼得
Free calls. Free internet. For everyone.
终生享有
Forever.
瓦伦丁的助手也有同样的植入伤疤
Valentine's assistant has the same implant scar.
我想我要会一会这个瓦伦丁先生了
I think Mr. Valentine and I shall have a tate-a-tate.
他下个星期会举办一个晚宴
He's having a gala dinner next week.
我会帮你弄到邀请函
I'll get you an invitation.
但是你一定要小心行事
You need to be careful though.
在你昏迷的这段期间 已经有上百个重要人物失踪了
Since you were out, hundreds of VIPs have gone missing.
没有勒索信 跟阿诺德教授的情况一模一样
No ransom notes, exactly like Professor Arnold.
那我建议你最好把我的资料
Then I suggest you make my alias
弄得漂漂亮亮的
somebody worth kidnapping.
你恐高吗
You don't like heights?
没事的 我之前试过
Yes it's okay I've done it before.
只要不去想它 就没事的
Probably alright if I don't think of it.
嘿 放心吧 你可是班里的最优生呢
Hey, you'll be alright, You're top of the class.
听好了 你们的任务就是
Listen up, your mission is to
要避开雷达检测 着陆在目标地点
land in the target without the radar detecting you.
如果你被雷达检测到 或没有降落到目标上 你就可以卷铺盖走人了
If I read you on the radar or you miss the target, you go home.
明白了吗
Is that understood?
二十秒后到达跳伞区域
Drop zone coming up. 20 seconds.
走吧
Here we go.
-我真的觉得我做不到啊 -你当然做不到了
- I really don't think I can do this. - Of course you can't.
往后站看我表演吧
Get to the back and I'll show you how, yeah.
艾格西 艾格西 等一下
Eggsy, Eggsy.. wait. Hang on.
洛克茜 别再犹豫了
Roxy, just stop fucking about.
跟着我跳 好吗
Follow me, yeah?
洛克茜 再不跳就来不及了
Roxy, it's now or never.
跳吧
Jump.
好姑娘 洛克茜 真高兴你做到了
Good girl, Rox. I'm glad you made it.
小家伙们 你们挺欢乐的啊
My my, you're all very cheerful.
你们真的以为会这么简单吗
You really think it was gonna be that straightforward?
傻子都能看懂平视显示器
Any idiot can read a heads-up display.
王牌特工必须学会
A Kingsman agent needs to be able
在高压下解决问题
to solve problems under pressure.
比如你们其中一人没有降落伞该怎么办
Like what to do when one of your group has no parachute.
没有降落伞 是谁
No parachute? Who?
靠 谁没有
Fuck. Which one?
我们该怎么做
What do we do?
告诉过你们 避开雷达检测 降落到目标地点
I told you. Aim for the target coming under the radar.
我希望不用为你们中的一个收尸
And I hope not to be scraping one of you up.
但如果你摔也能摔死在目标地点里
But if I do have to and you're inside the target...
我会对你刮目相看的
means I'll be very impressed.
大家听好 我有个计划
Everybody listen, I've got a plan.
两人一组 抓住离你最近的人
Pair up. Grab the closest person to you.
鲁弗斯 过来
Rufus, come on.
该死
Oh fuck.
鲁弗斯
Rufus!
见鬼 我不行
Oh shit! I can't
操你妹
Fuck!!!
吓死我了
Fucking cock.
鲁弗斯 你个混蛋
Rufus, you wanker.
现在我们人数变奇数了
We are an odd number now.
-快 围成一圈 -靠 没错 照他说的做
- Quick, make a circle. - Fuck. Right boys. Let's do it.
我们一个接着一个的打开降落伞
We'll pull our cords one by one.
一知道谁没有降落伞 他右边的人就要抓住他
When we know who's it, the person on the right grabs him.
好的 艾格西
Ok, Eggsy
这计划很好 艾格西 你们还有三十秒 动作快点吧
Good plan, Eggsy. You have 30 seconds. Come on now. Hurry up.
你先开始
You first.
靠
Fuck
好了 接下来是我
OK, Me next.
地上见 兄弟们
See you on the ground, boys.
该我了
Now me.
洛克茜 不管接下来发生什么 我都会保护你的 知道吗
Roxy, no matter what happens now, I've got you. Alright?
好 艾格西
OK, Eggsy
你先来 好吗
You first, okay?
好
Yep
该死
Shit.
我去
Oh Shit.
洛克茜
Rox
雨果 迪格比
Hugo, Digby,
你们没降落在我们的标志上 你们也不是我们的一员了
You don't land in the K then you're not in the K.
鲁弗斯 你过早打开降落伞
Rufus, you opened too soon.
完全暴露在了雷达下
You were all over the radar.
你们三个 收拾行李回家吧
All three of you, pack your bags. Go home.
艾格西 洛克茜 恭喜
Eggsy, Roxy, congratulations.
你们刷新了记录
You have set a new record.
离地三百英尺的时候才打开降落伞 胆子够大
Opening at 300 feet, that's pretty ballsy.
任务完成地很漂亮 解散
Well done on completing another task. Follow.
抱歉 长官 但是我想问一下为什么选我做倒霉鬼
Sorry sir, but why the fuck you choose me as the gimp?
我是随用随抛的小棋子吗
- Am I the expendable candidate?
不不不 你别用那种语气和我说话
- No no no. You don't talk to me like that.
有什么怨言的话 过来在我耳边说
If you have a complaint, you came here and you whisper in my ear.
肩膀上背那么重的东西你不累吗
You need to take that jape off your shoulder.
德维尔先生 很高兴见到你
Mr. DeVere. It's a pleasure to meet you.
抱歉 看来是我记错日子了
I am sorry. I seem to have my dates muddles up.
哦 不 不 我为了您把酒会取消了
Oh no no. I canceled the gala because of you.
如此慷慨捐赠的贵客
Anybody willing to donate that much
理当享用专属的晚餐 请进
deserves their own dinner. Come in.
谢谢
Thank you.
不得不承认 我一直想方设法想要和您见上一面
Gotta admit, I was really intrigued to meet you.
没有几个亿万富翁是我不认识的
There are not many billionaires I do not know.
这一点我毫不怀疑
I don't doubt it.
显然 我让我手下的人调查了一些关于您的事情
Obviously, I have had my people looking into your affairs
您的祖上真是家财万贯啊
and that's some pretty old money you're from.
敢问您的父母是怎么做到的啊
How'd your folks make it?
大多数是地产 不动产交易
Property, mostly. Property in the markets.
没有什么见不得人的 如果这是你担心的是这方面
Nothing personal, if that's your concern.
不 我只是想了解一下
No, I'm just in to find out what
您是什么样的人 我相信您一定会理解的
kind of person you are. I'm sure you understand that.
当然理解
I most certainly do.
希望您饿了
Hope you're hungry.
我快饿死了
I'm famished.
很好 请坐
Good. Grab a seat.
请给我来一份巨无霸 谢谢
I'll have the Big Mac, please.
选的好
Great choice.
但是没有什么比加了秘密酱汁的双层起司汉堡更美味的了
But nothing beats two cheeseburgers with secret sauce.
配上这45年的拉菲 味道美极了
Tastes great with this '45 Lafite.
经典的搭配
A classic pairing.
不过餐后甜点我推荐1937年的依坤宫葡萄酒配布丁
May I suggest Twinkies with 1937 Chateau d'Yquem for pudding?
我喜欢
I like it.
您想捐钱给我的基金会
So you want to donate to my foundation?
可是 您是知道我在那个领域遇到了瓶颈的 对吧
You are aware that I wind things down in that area, right?
气候变化对我们每个人来说都是威胁 瓦伦丁先生
Climate changes is a threat which affect us all, Mr. Valentine.
你是为数不多和我
And you are one of the few
看法一致的大人物之一
powerful people who seems to share my concerns.
我放慢了进程是因为没有任何进展
I stepped things down because I wasn't getting anywhere.
每一项研究都指向同一结果
Every bit of research kept pointing to the same thing.
二氧化碳的排放只是个幌子
The carbon emissions are a red herring, and we are past the
无论我们想怎样弥补都无济于事了
point of no return no matter what remedial actions we take.
看来您知道得很清楚嘛
You know your shit.
我有时候会很嫉妒那些
I sometimes envy the blissful ignorance of those less well-versed
什么都不懂的傻白甜
in their shit.
阿诺德教授常说
As Professor Arnold always said:
人类是唯一一种明知宿主很脆弱
"Humankind is the only virus cursed to live with the
却还是寄生在里面的病毒
horrifying knowledge of its host's fragile mortality."
知道他的人可并不多
There are not a lot of people who know about him.
您喜欢间谍电影吗 德维尔先生
Do you like spy movies, Mr. DeVere?
近代的间谍电影对我来说 有点太严肃了
Nowadays, they're all a little serious for my taste.
但是那些老电影 还是非常棒的
But the old ones... marvelous.
随时奉上夸张的戏剧情节
Give me a farfetched theatrical plot any day.
那些老版的邦德电影 哦 天啊
The old Bond movies. Oh, man.
啊 那是我儿时的梦想职业
Ah, When I was a kid, that was my dream job.
一个绅士特工
A gentleman spy.
我认为邦德系列电影中
I always felt the old
最引人注目的还是反派
Bond films were only as good as the villain.
我小的时候 更想做一个未来主义的自大狂
As a child, I rather fancied a futuristic colorful megalomaniac.
只可惜我们都要长大
What a shame we both had to grow up.
吃好喝好啊
Bon appetit.
给我几天时间考虑一下您的提议
Just give me a couple of days to think over your proposal.
我会派人和您的人联系 一切都没问题的
I'll have my people get in touch with yours and it's all good.
谢谢你的 “开心乐园餐”
Thank you for such a "Happy Meal".
-你想让我去跟踪他吗 -不用
- Well, you want me to follow him? - Nah.
我在酒里放了纳米追踪装置
I put a nano tracker gel in the wine.
接下来的二十四小时 他的动向尽在我们掌握之中
We'll know his every move for the next 24 hours.
最终会找出他在为谁工作的
Finally find out who he works for.
瓦伦丁不让我离开他的视线
Valentine didn't let me out of his sight.
我只在进屋的路上拍到了这个
All I got was this, on the way in.
南格莱德教会是位于肯塔基州的一个仇恨团体
South Glade Mission Church is a hate group based in Kentucky.
南格莱德教会
拯救美国
FBI监视他们很多年了
The FBI have been monitoring them for years.
你认为瓦伦丁是拥护者吗
Do you think Valentine is a supporter?
现在还没有证据证明他们有直接联系 但是我会留意的
No evidence yet of a direct connection, but I'll keep looking.
哦 顺便说下
Oh, by the way,
人数不断增多的失踪名单
the ever-growing list of missing persons...
又加上了斯堪的纳维亚的皇室成员
Now includes Scandinavian Royalty.
蒂尔德公主
Royal Crown Princess Tilde.
放我出去 你个疯子
Just let me out, you PSYCHO!
我告诉过你了 你想走随时都可以走
I told you, you're free to go anytime you want.
只要你同意我的条件
As long as you agree to my conditions.
我不同意
I don't agree.
我绝对 永远都不会同意的
And I am never ever going to agree!
够了
Enough yet.
贱人
Bitch.
近几周 不断有
The list of missing celebrities and
名流和高官无故失踪
dignitaries has continued to grow in recent weeks.
世界各国领导人被社会各方施压
And world leaders are coming
要求给出答复
under increasing pressure to provide answers.
我们会动用一切力量来寻找蒂尔德公主
We are doing everything in our power to find princess Tilde.
公主失踪
各界政府和安保部队正在合作
You know, governments and
已经开始在世界范围内展开搜寻
security forces worldwide are working together...
一定会将绑架案的幕后黑手绳之于法
to find the person behind these abductions.
另一则新闻 全世界的人们都夜以继日地排队
In other news, people all over the world continue to
来领取一张免费的手机卡
wait in line day and night to get their free SIM card.
P夫人 你也领到了
Mrs. P. You get one?
是啊 我排了一整天的队
Yeah, I've been queuing up all day.
这场由慈善家里奇蒙·瓦伦丁先生发起的
This unprecedented giveaway
大批民众排队领取瓦丁伦电话卡
史无前例的赠送活动
by the philanthropist Richmond Valentine...
已经赠送出超过十亿张手机卡了
has already seen over a billion cards distributed.
稍息
At ease.
你们以为这一天就轻轻松松过去了吗
So you thought you were done for the day, huh?
没那么简单
Probably not.
-参加派对 -今晚 在伦敦
- A party? - Tonight. In London.
-这是谁 -你们的目标
- Who is this? - Your target.
你们的任务是用你们神经语言程式学的训练成果
Your mission is to use your NLP Training to win over
来搞定照片中的人
the individual in the photograph in your envelope.
我说的搞定 意思是完全拿下
And when I say "Win over", I do mean in the Biblical sense.
简单
Easy
男不坏女不爱
Most girls love a bit rough.
我们走着瞧
We'll see about that, yeah.
看谁能搞定这姑娘
We certainly will.
我忍不住过来想告诉你 你的眼睛真美
I just had to come over and say "Amazing eyes".
-你戴了彩色美瞳吗 -才没有
- You wearing color contacts? - No.
-才怪咧 -你不是吧 贬低批评法 真搞笑
- You so are. - Oh my god. 'Negging'. That's hilarious.
那是九十年代搭讪的方法
I haven't had anyone try that since the 90s.
请问你说什么
Excuse me?
贬低批评法 是指说一些故意贬低批评的话
"Negging". Saying something negative to a pretty
来削弱一个漂亮姑娘的社会价值
girl in order to undermine her social value.
是为了让你想要赢得他的肯定
Its supposed to make you want to win his approval.
是最基础的神经语言学的谈话技巧
Absurdly basic neurolinguistic programming technique.
是我的问题吗 还是这香槟的味道真的有点怪
Is it just me or does this champagne taste a little bit funny?
是你品位不够 伙计
That's an acquired taste, mate.
我觉得这香槟是次品
- I think it's just cheap.
你可以试试这个 味道不错
- Get one of these instead. They're delicious.
如果你对搭讪技巧感兴趣的话
You know, if you're interested
这人绝对是专家
in ornamental techniques, this guy is textbook.
看到他刚才的方法了吗 叫做岔开话题
See what he just did? Its called an 'opinion opener.
他会提出一个不痛不痒的问题
He got you talking with a neutral question...
让我们所有人都参与其中
got all of us involved in the conversation,
所以你就会渴望得到他的关注
so that you crave individual attention.
不 我只是觉得香槟味道有点奇怪
Nah, I'm just saying that the champagne tastes weird...
索菲亚·蒙塔古·赫灵小姐 前台有您的电话
Lady Sophie Montague Herring, phone call for you at reception.
-我马上回来 -一会见哟
- Be right back. - See you in a bit, yeah.
-你用错方法了 洛克茜 太过强硬 -你还好吗
-Bad job, Rox. I'm feeling a bit rough. - You alright?
抱歉我无意中听到了
Sorry to eavesdrop...
但是有更简单的方法可以把人带回家
but there is a much easier way to guarantee getting someone home.
催眠药
Rohypnol.
或者更猛的料
Or even something stronger.
你到底是谁
Who the fuck are you?
我在哪
Where am I?
这把刀可以救你的命
This knife can save your life.
操
Fuck
我的老板有两个问题问你 艾格西
My employer's got two questions for you, Eggsy.
王牌特工是什么东西 还有哈利·哈特是谁
What the fuck is Kingsman? And who is Harry Hart?
我不知道那是什么 该死
I do not know what the fuck that is. shit!
噢 艾格西 我刚刚杀了你的那两位朋友
Oh Eggsy, I just killed two of your friends
因为他们给了我同样的狗屁答案
because they gave me the same bullshit answer.
快剪断这该死的绳子 求你了
Just cut the fucking ropes, please.
艾格西 王牌特工值得为之丧命吗
Eggsy, is the Kingsman worth dying for?
去死吧
Fuck You
恭喜你
Congratulations.
做得非常好
Bloody well done.
-其他人怎么样了 -洛克茜轻松通过了
- How'd the others do? - Roxy passed with flying colors.
查理是下一个
Charlie's up next.
想看看吗
Want to watch?
好啊 可以啊
Yeah, alright.
王牌特工真的值得你为之丧命吗
Is Kingsman really worth dying for?
不 当然不值得 我全都告诉你 求你放了我
No fuck, it isn't shit I'll tell all you want, please.
彻斯特·金就是亚瑟
Chester King's Arthur,
是一个叫王牌特工的间谍组织的头儿
head of a spy agency; It's called Kingsman.
谢谢你 查理 非常感谢
Thank you Charlie. Much appreciated.
快点 我们不是说好了吗
Come on, It wasn't the fucking deal
我对你寄予了如此厚望
I had such high hopes for you.
你太丢人了
You are a bloody disgrace.
对不起
I'm so sorry
给我解开吧
Please untie me.
你自己解吧
Untie yourself.
亚瑟 求你了
Arthur, please.
有人吗 别这样
Anyone?...No
加拉哈德 珀西瓦尔 恭喜你们
Galahad, Percival. Congratulations.
你们的候选人进入
You candidates have reached
最后的测试阶段了
the final stage of the testing process.
按照惯例 你们有二十四小时的时间一起相处
As tradition allows, you now have 24 hours to spend with them.
艾格西 你应该知道
Eggsy, you should know
你的父亲来到了这个阶段
your father reached this point.
从现在起
From now on,
不会再有安全保障了 明白吗
there are no safety nets. Understood?
很好 解散
Good. Dismissed.
查理 你该回家了
Charlie, time to go home.
去你的
Fuck you
我要告诉我粑粑
My fucking dad's gonna hear about this.
“尿还是不尿”
"To pee or not to pee?"
那是我在巴黎拆除一颗
That was the headline the
脏弹之后第二天的报纸头条
day after I diffused a dirty bomb in Paris.
-“德国比英格兰 一比五” - 我错过了那场比赛
- "Germany 1 - England 5." - I missed that game.
当时我在五角大楼里大战一个地下特工组织
I was breaking up an undercover spy ring at Pentagon.
我的第一项任务
My first mission.
我阻止了刺杀玛格丽特·撒切尔夫人的阴谋
I foiled the assassination of Margaret Thatcher.
不是所有人都因此感谢你
Not everybody had thanked you for that one.
事实上 艾格西 没有任何人为我完成任务而感谢我
The point is, Eggsy, nobody thanked me for any of them.
这些头版新闻 都只是名人的花边新闻
Front page news, and all these occasions were celebrity nonsense.
因为王牌特工的成就
Because it is the nature of
注定永远都是秘密
Kingsman that our achievements remain secret.
一位绅士的名字
A gentleman's name should
一生中只应在报纸上出现三次
appear in the newspaper only three times:
出生时 结婚时和去世时
When he's born, when he marries and when he dies.
而我们 首当其要的是 要做一名绅士
And we are, first and foremost, gentlemen.
挺操蛋的啊
Pretty fucked then.
就像查理说的 我只是个平民百姓
Its like Charlie said, I am just a pleb.
胡扯 英雄向来
Nonesense. Being a gentleman has nothing
不问出处
to do with the circumstances of one's birth.
做一名绅士是个逐步学习的过程
Being a gentleman is something one learns.
是呀 但要怎么学啊
Yeah, but how?
好吧 第一课
Alright, first lesson,
落座前你应该征得我的同意
you should have asked me before you took a seat.
第二课
Second lesson,
学会调制一杯好的马丁尼鸡尾酒
how to make a proper martini.
好的 哈利
Yes, Harry.
该死的 这好疼啊
Goddamn it. It fucking hurts.
是你要求配备生物识别安全系统的
You are the one who asked for a biometric security system.
就弄个简单开关不行吗
What's wrong with a simple switch?
弄个简单开关
A simple switch?
这是一台极其危险的机器
This is an extremely dangerous machine.
它应该由理智而富有责任感的人来操作 比如我
It should only be operated by someone responsible and sane as me.
要是它落入坏人手里那就糟了
Bad shit can happen if it falls into the wrong hands.
掌纹同步完成
认证有效
-我们做完了吗  -没 还有这台
- Are we done here? Shit - No, now this one,
教堂测试用的
for the test of the church.
这台工作范围小 用简单的开关就行了
This one just has a short range. A simple switch will do.
那么你打算像《窈窕淑女》里那样教我如何发音讲话吗
So you gonna teach me how to talk proper like in 'My Fair Lady'?
那太可笑了
That'd be absurd.
做一名绅士和他的口音没有任何关系
Being a gentleman has nothing to do with one's accent.
而是要由内而外的散发出绅士风度
It's about being at ease in one's own skin.
正如海明威所说
As Hemingway said:"There is
“强于别人并不高贵”
nothing noble in being superior to your fellow man."
“真正的高贵是强于曾经的自己”
"True nobility is being superior to your former self."
现在 每一位绅士首先需要的 是一套好的西装
Now, the first thing every gentleman needs is a good suit.
我指的是一套全定制的西装 而不是成衣
By which I mean a bespoke suit. Never off the peg.
而王牌特工的西装永远是防弹的
And Kingsman suits are always bulletproof,
所以 来给你量量尺寸吧
So let's get you measured.
不管你得没得到这份工作 你都将拥有
And whether you get the job or not, you will have a
关于特工学院永久而有用的记忆
lasting and useful memento of your time at Kingsman.
对不起 先生 但是有位先生正在量身
I'm so sorry, sir, but a gentleman is completing his fitting.
可以用二号更衣室
Fitting Room 2 is available.
定做第一套衣服的时候
One does not use Fitting Room 2...
怎么能用二号更衣室呢
when one is popping one's cherry.
或许在我们等待的时候 我该带你去参观下三号更衣室
Perhaps I'll show you Fitting Room 3, while we wait.
-我们是上去还是下去 -都不是
- So we going up or down? - Neither.
-就这样吗 -当然不是 拉一下你左边的挂钩
- Is this it? - Of course not. Pull the hook on your left.
噢 天呐
Oh, Yes
太 太棒了
Very very nice.
你需要一双鞋子来搭配你的西装
You're going to need a pair of shoes to go with your suit.
牛津鞋是带有开放式襟片的皮鞋
An Oxford is any formal shoe, with open lacing.
这种有额外装饰花纹的叫做布洛克鞋
This additional decorative piece is called broguing.
-“牛津胜于布洛克” -一生铭记 艾格西
- "Oxford's, not brogue's." - Words to live by, Eggsy.
一生铭记
Words to live by.
试一双吧
Try a pair.
顺便提一句 你的武器得分很棒
Your weapon scores are excellent, by the way.
这些都是你熟悉的
These you're familiar with.
而这是我们标准配备的手枪
And this is our standard issue pistol.
它很独特 如你所见 它也能在
It's quite unique. As you all see it, it also fires a
近距离情况下发射猎枪弹
shotgun cartridge for use in messy close-range situations.
-感觉怎么样 -可以 挺合适 -现在展示一下
How do they feel? Yeah,good. Now do your very best in impersonation
德国贵族正式问候礼仪
of a German aristocrat's formal greeting.
不是这样的 艾格西
No, Eggsy.
好厉害
That is sick.
在以前 脚后跟还有手机呢
In the old days, they had a phone in the heel as well.
我怎么把它弄回去
How do I get it back in?
它上面涂有一种发作时间最快的
It is coated with one of the fastest-acting
致死神经毒素 所以一定要非常小心
neurotoxins known to man, so very carefully.
我很喜欢这个
I had a lot of fun with this.
我们的化学工程里最精美的范例之一
One of our finest examples of chemical engineering.
毒药 喝下的时候是无毒的
Poison. Harmless when ingested.
不过到了你合适的时机
But at a time, convenient to you...
它可以被远程激活
it can be remotely activated.
准备模式
Primed.
致命模式
Lethal.
那这些呢 是干什么用的 电人的吗
And what about these? What do these do? Electrocute you?
-别想多了 这是手榴弹 -不是吧
- Don't be ridiculous. It's a hand grenade. - Shut up...
如果你想电击某人 你需要一只图章戒指
If you want to electrocute someone, you'll need a signet ring.
绅士通常会把图章戒者戴在左手
A gentleman traditionally wears the signet on his left hand, but
但是王牌特工则戴在他的利手
a Kingsman wears it on whatever hand happens to be dominant.
如果你按下戒指背面的传感器
If you touch the contact behind the ring,
它会产生五万伏的电压
it delivers 50,000 volts.
这些呢 这些有什么特别的
And what about them? What makes them so special?
没什么特别 那项技术落后于特工界了
Nothing. That technology is caught up with the spy world.
放回去 艾格西
Put it back, Eggsy.
时间正好 那位绅士正好更衣完毕
Perfect timing. Gentleman's just finished.
德维尔先生
Mr. DeVere.
多巧呀
What a coincidence.
我会来这儿都是因为你呢
You're totally the reason I'm here.
你离开我家之后 我就一直在
When you left my house, I was
找你那天穿的那种帅爆了的外套
searching for that dope-ass smoking jacket you had on.
因为我要参加英国皇家赛马会
And since I'm going as Royal Ascot,
显然就需要一件这样的长尾服
apparently you need one of these penguin suits...
所以我就来了 你来这做什么呢
Here I am. What are you doing here?
你好啊 小伙儿 我是里奇蒙·瓦丁伦
What's up man? Richmond Valentine.
这是我新的贴身男仆 我刚刚在把他介绍给我的裁缝
This is my new valet. I was just introducing him to my tailor.
又巧了 我也是
Another coincidence. So am I.
你有好好考虑过
- Did you have any chance to
-我的提议吗 -当然了
think further on my proposal? - Most definitely.
我的人很快就会联系你
My people will be getting in touch with you very soon.
我保证
I guarantee it.
提个建议 赛马会要戴圆顶高帽
A word of advice: Ascot requires top hat.
我建议你到 落扣帽商 那里买
I might suggest Lock & Co. Hatters,
在圣詹姆斯街
St. James.
是烙鱼的烙吗
"Lox", as in smoked fish?
是落网的“落”
As in "Locked up".
有时候我真的听不懂你们的话
I have trouble understanding you people sometimes.
你们说话发音太有趣了
You all talk so funny.
先生 你能给他量下身吗
Gentlemen, would you look after him please?
现在有一顶酷毙了的圆顶礼帽了
Now this is a dope-ass top hat.
加塞尔 咱们去赛马会吧
Gazelle, lets go Ascotting.
你的帽子可以了 快点 我要去见女王 别让我迟到了
Your hat is fine Bill, come on. Don't make me late for the queen.
快点 加塞尔 我们要迟到了
Come on, Gazelle. We're gonna be late.
赛马会有多远 多远
How far is Ascot? How far?
梅林说你要见我 先生
Merlin said you wanted to see me, sir?
坐
Sit down.
漂亮的小狗 什么名字
Pretty dog. What's his name?
JB
J.B.
-出自詹姆斯·邦德吗 -不是
- As in "James Bond"? - No.
-杰森·伯恩 -不是 是杰克·鲍尔
- "Jason Bourne"? - No. Jack Bauer.
好名字
Bravo.
虽然我不愿意承认 艾格西 但是我觉得
It pains me to admit it, Eggsy, but I think that
总有一天你会成为一名像他们一样出色的特工
one day you might be as good a spy as any of them.
拿着
Take it.
开枪杀了这只狗
Shoot the dog.
这枪已经上膛了
This weapon is live.
开枪杀了这只狗
Shoot the dog.
把枪给我
Give me the gun.
至少那个女孩有种
At least the girl's got balls,
出去吧
Get out.
我知道你做不到的
I knew you couldn't make it.
回家吧
Go home.
梅林 让洛克茜过来
Merlin, send in Roxy, please.
欢迎加入王牌特工 兰斯洛特
Welcome to Kingsman, Lancelot.
噢 天啊 我一直很担心你
Oh god, I've been so worried about you.
噢 我的小戴西 看看你现在多大了
Oh my Dais, look how big you've got.
-他在哪 -我没事
- Where is he? - I am fine.
艾格西 别去 别理这事
Eggsy, please please, just don't get involved...
不 我不该留下你独自一人的
No, I should never have left you on your own.
现在这一切该结束了
This stops right now.
我马上就回来
Be right back.
噢 小混蛋 你回来了
Oh Mugsy, so you're back?
还偷了辆出租车
You nicked a fucking taxi now?
没错 我能和你聊聊我妈妈的黑眼圈是怎么回事吗
Yeah. Can I have a word about my mom's black eye?
你想跟我谈 那就从车里出来
You wanna have a word with me, you get out of that cab,
我把你打回娘胎去
I'll knock you straight back down on your fucking arse.
让你的马仔进去 我就出来
Tell your muppets to go inside, then I'll get out.
进去吧 小伙子们 两招就搞定他了
Go on lads. There'll be two hits.
我打他一拳 他就倒地了
Me hitting him and him hitting the floor.
来吧 臭小子 让我看看你有什么本事
Come on in, you prick. Let's see what you got, eh.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你这胆小鬼 你干什么
You mug. What are you doing?
夹着尾巴逃了么
Now you ain't got no bollocks?
让我下去 他打了我的妈妈
Come on, he'll beat my fucking mother.
等你牙长齐了再来吧 小蠢货
Come back when you've grown a pair. Mugsy.
你失去了成为
You throw away
王牌特工的机会
your biggest opportunity
就因为一条狗
over a fucking dog.
然后你又偷了我老板的车 让我难堪
And then you humiliate me by stealing my boss's car.
你为了得到这份工作竟然杀了只狗
You shot a dog just to get a fucking job?
是的
Yes, I did.
每次我上厕所的时候 泡菜先生都会让我想起那一刻
Mr Pickle here reminds me of that every time I take a shit.
你杀了你的狗然后把它做成了标本
You shot your dog and had it stuffed?
你真变态
You fucking freak.
不是 是我用枪打了我的狗
No. I shot my dog and
然后把它带回家
then I brought him home and continued to care
整整养了十一年 直到它死于胰腺炎
for him for the next eleven years until he died of pancreatitis.
-什么 -那是空弹 艾格西
- What? - It was a blank, Eggsy.
只是空弹而已
It was a fucking blank.
还记得阿米莉亚么
Remember Amelia?
记得
Yeah
她并没有淹死
She didn't drown. She works
她在我们柏林的技术部门工作 活得好好的
in our tech department in Berlin. She's fine.
我们必须测试你们的极限
Limits must be tested. A Kingsman
一个王牌特工只有为了救人才能去冒生命危险
only condones the risking of a life to save another.
就像你当初搞砸了 我父亲救了你一命那样吗
As my father saved your life even though your fuck-up cost his?
你为什么不把他也做成标本放在这儿呢
What you've get him stuffed here also?
你难道看不出来
Can't you see that everything
我现在做的一切都是为了报答他么
I have done has been about trying to repay him?
哈利 听着
Harry, listen to this.
瓦伦丁那边有动静了
Valentine's alarm is saying something of note.
你知道为什么我喜欢用笔和纸吗
You know what I love about pen and paper?
因为没有人可以黑进来
Nobody can hack into this shit.
我们的环球之旅获得了巨大的成功
Our worldwide tour was a complete success.
我们全部都搞定了
We have total coverall.
-就像宾果游戏里把数字划掉一样 -宾果
- Like when all your numbers in bingo are crossed out. - Bingo!
宾果 一种游戏 你玩过吧
Bingo, the game. You have played Bingo, right?
我看起来像是玩宾果游戏的人么
Do I look like I play bingo?
重点是
Point is...
如果我们在教堂的计划进行顺利 我们就可以放心开始了
if our tests go well at church tomorrow, we are good to go.
南格莱德教会
South Glade Mission Church.
-梅林 把飞机准备好 -没问题
- Merlin, get the plane ready. - Will do
-我很抱歉 我可以 -你应该觉得抱歉
- I am so sorry. I'm gonna do.. - You should be.
待在这儿 等我回来再来收拾你这个烂摊子
You stay right there. I'll sort this mess out when I get back.
肯塔基州 美国
让我告诉你们 见证这一切
And I say to you: Bear witness.
看看新闻吧
Watch the news. Watch the news.
艾滋 洪水 还有无辜生命的鲜血
AIDS, floods The blood of the innocents spilled.
有人怀疑这上帝的愤怒
And yet there are those who doubt this is the wrath of God.
我们肮脏的政府纵容同性恋
Our filthy government condones sodomy.
离婚 堕胎
Divorce, abortion.
还有人在怀疑
And yet some still doubt,
这是反基督者的杰作
this is the work of the Antichrist.
哪怕你不是犹太人 黑人 妓女
You do not have to be a Jew, a nigger, a whore...
或者只是一个崇尚科学的进化论支持者
or an atheistic science loving evolution spouter.
很好的布道
Charming sermon.
你看见瓦伦丁了吗
Can you see Valentine anywhere?
我的朋友们 虽然他是一个公正的上帝
So my friends, although he is a just God, he is justly...
南格莱德教会
美国注定
失败
他也别无他选了
The One and there will be no turning back
你确定我们不在范围之内吗
Are you sure we are out of range?
我们在一千英尺英尺开外呢 怎么了
We're over a 1000 feet away. What's wrong?
如果我们的计算出错了呢
- What if the calculations are wrong?
你只要相信我就好
- You just have to trust me.
犹太人 黑人 同性恋
Jews, nigger, fag lovers.
恶魔将用永恒的烈火灼烧他们
And the devil is burning them for all eternity.
借过一下
Excuse me.
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?
嘿 你有毛病吗
Hey, what's your problem?
我是个信仰天主教的男妓
I am a Catholic whore, currently enjoying congress
现在我正和我的犹太黑人男友搞婚外情
out of wedlock with my black Jewish boyfriend...
而且他还在军队的流产门诊工作
who works in a military abortion clinic.
撒旦万岁 祝您有个美好的下午 女士
So hail Satan. And have a lovely afternoon, madam.
该死 他要走了 我现在要开始测试了
Oh shit, he's leaving. I'm starting the test now.
希望他们这群人都用了我们的手机卡
Hope enough of these freaks have our SIM cards.
让你坐下
Ask you to sit down...
你就像个异教徒一样离开这里
You do not leave this church like the infidel you are.
你会吃掉你的孩子
You will eat your babies.
你会在上帝的鲜血里溺毙
You will drown in the blood of the Lord.
上帝是不会拯救你的
He will not save you.
靠
Holy fuck.
我简直不忍心看 快过来
Shit, I can't watch this. Get over here.
我的天啊
Jesus...
加拉哈德 你能听到吗
Galahad, can you hear me?
哈利 哈利 你到底怎么了
Harry, Harry.. what the heck is going on?
把声音关小点吧
Just turn the volume down please.
我没想到会这么有效
I didn't expect it to be that effective.
影响率如何
What kind of response are we talking of?
100%
100%.
不管有没有用电话卡 所有人都被影响到了吗
So everyone's been infected Whether they have SIM card or not?
而且还给我们带来了点额外好处 刚好除掉王牌特工
And its added benefit of wiping out the Kingsman.
暂时还没有
Not yet.
你得过来看看
Oh you need to see this.
你对我做了什么 我控制不了自己
What did you do to me? I had no control.
我杀了所有人
I killed all those people.
-是我自愿杀的 -很聪明的发明 不是么
- I wanted to. - Clever, isn't it?
简单来说 就是一种神经电波
In simple terms, its a neurological wave that triggers
能够激起人们的好斗情绪 并且关闭人们的抑制能力
the centers of aggression and switches off inhibitor.
我猜你是通过你那该死的电话卡发射的电波 对吗
Transmitted through your nasty free SIM cards, I assume?
你知道现在像什么吗
You know what this is like?
就像我们都爱看的老电影
Its like those old movies we both love.
我现在要告诉你我的全部计划
Now I'm gonna tell you my whole plan...
然后我会想出一些荒唐的
and then I'm gonna come up with some absurd,
复杂的方法来杀掉你
convoluted way to kill you...
然后你就会想出一个同样复杂的方法来逃脱
and then you'll find an equally convoluted way to escape.
听起来挺好啊
That sounds good to me.
可惜 现实和电影还是有区别的
Well, this ain't that kind of movie.
不
No!
他死了吗
Is he dead?
你开枪爆了一个人的头 通常他都会死的
That's usually what happens when you shoot someone in the head.
-感觉很爽 对么 -不 不
- It feels good, Right? - No no,
感觉不爽 我感觉糟透了
it does not feel good. It felt fucking awful.
为什么 你刚刚杀了教堂里那么多的人
What? You just killed how many people in that church.
这才区区一个人而已
This is one guy.
不 他们是自相残杀的
No..No... No, they killed each other.
现在开始倒计时吧
Okay, send off the countdown clock
派对明天开始
This party starts tomorrow.
亚瑟
Arthur?
-你在吗 -很遗憾 我在
- Are you there? - Sadly, I am.
集合所有的王牌特工
Assemble the Kingsman.
你看不出来我做的一切
Can't you see that everything
都是为了报答他吗
I have done has been about trying to repay him?
我看见一个充满潜力的年轻人
I see a young man with potential,
一个想在有生之年出人头地的年轻人
who wants to do something good with his life.
亚瑟 哈利死了
Arthur, Harry is dead.
加拉哈德死了
Galahad is dead.
因此 我们刚敬了他一杯
Hence, we have just drunk a toast to him.
你现在知道那个疯子在做什么了
Well then you know what that psycho's doing.
世界上有多少人在用那张电话卡
How many people in the world have got those SIM cards?
瓦伦丁可以给任何一个人发送信号
Valentine can send a signal to any of them.
所有的人 如果他们同时开始暴走 那么
All of them. If they all go homicidal at the same time, then..
的确 多亏了加拉哈德的影像资料
Indeed, and thanks to Galahad recordings
我们有了瓦伦丁的罪证
we have Valentine's confession.
这些情报已经递交给了有关部门
The intelligence has been passed on to the relevant authorities.
我们的任务已经完成了
Our work is complete.
这也是我们已经陨落的朋友留下的最宝贵的遗产
And a most distinguished legacy for our fallen friend it is too.
这就完了
And that's it?
过来坐下 孩子
Come sit down, boy.
这是1815年拿破仑时期的白兰地
This is an 1815 Napoleonic brandy.
我们只在失去一位王牌特工的时候才喝
And we only drink it when we lose a Kingsman.
加拉哈德很看重你
Galahad was very fond of you.
既然如此 我想我们稍微破一下例
And on this occasion, I think it is acceptable for us...
也未尝不可
to bend the rules a little.
-他们都是王牌特工吗 -是的 都是我们的奠基者
- These are all Kingsmen? - Yes, our founder members.
来一起祝酒吧
I want you to join me in a toast.
敬加拉哈德
To Galahad.
哈利说你不喜欢违反规则
Harry said you don't like to break the rules, often.
为什么现在为我破例
Why now?
你很优秀 艾格西
You're very good, Eggsy.
也许我会提议让你继承加拉哈德的位置
Perhaps I'll make you my proposal for Galahad's position.
如果我们在某些政治问题上
Provided we can see eye to eye
站在同一条阵线上的话
on certain political matters.
你能猜到
Can you guess..
这是什么吗
What this is?
我不用猜 哈利告诉我了
I don't have to. Harry showed it.
你按一下 我就会死
You click it, I die.
我就觉得那杯白兰地味道怪怪的
I thought that brandy tasted a bit shit.
很棒
Bravo.
瓦伦丁收买了你
Valentine won you over. Somehow
他一解释 我就明白了
Once he explained, I understood.
你被病毒感染 就会发烧
When you get a virus, you get a fever.
这是人体
That's the human body
在提高温度来杀死病毒
raising its core temperature to kill the virus.
地球也一样 全球变暖就是地球在发烧
Planet Earth works the same way: Global warming is the fever...
人类就是病毒
Mankind is the virus.
我们让地球生病了
We are making our planet sick.
一场屠杀是我们唯一的希望
A cull is our only hope.
如果我们自主减少我们的人口
If we do not reduce our population ourselves,
那么只会出现两种结局
there's only two ways this can go:
宿主杀死病毒 或者病毒杀死宿主
The host kills the virus, or the virus kills the host.
-不管是哪种方式 -结果都是一样
- Either way... - The result is the same:
病毒被消灭
The virus dies.
所以瓦伦丁想要自己解决人口问题
So Valentine's gonna take care of the population problem himself.
如果我们不自己采取行动 大自然也会行动的
If we don't do something, Nature will.
有时候 屠杀是保证
Sometimes a culling is the
我们物种活下来的唯一方式
only way to ensure that this species survives.
历史会见证瓦伦丁
And History will see Valentine
成为那个拯救人类灭亡的人
as the man who saved humanity from extinction.
所以他有权选择谁应该被杀 是么
And he gets to pick and choose who gets culled, does he?
所有那些他的富豪朋友们 都可以活下来
All his rich mates, they get to live.
还有那些他认为值得活下来的人 他都会保证他们安全
And anyone he thinks its worth saving, he's keeping them safe.
-不管是否他们同意他的做法 -还有你 艾格西
- Whether they agree with him or not. - And you, Eggsy.
看在哈利的份上 我邀请你成为新世界的一员
In Harry's honor, I am inviting you to be part of a new world.
现在是你做决定的时候了
It's time to make your decision.
我宁愿去追随哈利而去
I would rather be with Harry.
多谢你的好意
Thanks.
那就这样吧
So be it.
我们这种普通人的问题就在于
The problem with us common types is,
我们喜欢做些小动作
that we are light fingered.
王牌特工教会了我很多
Kingsman's taught me a lot.
但是论手法
But sleight of hand...
是的 他们都是我们的奠基人
Yes, they're our our founder members.
我早就学会了
I had that done already.
你这个愚蠢的小王八蛋
You dirty little fucking prick.
胜利日来临倒计时
请到安全区域
或前往
以下地址
没关系的 兰斯洛特 把枪放下 他已经通过验证了
It's okay, Lancelot. Put it down. It's verified.
亚瑟的电话刚刚收到了一条消息
Arthur's phone's just received an update text about
要转移到安全地方 我们的时间不多了
getting to safety. We don't have a lot time.
-你准备怎么做 -应该说是我们准备怎么做
- What you gonna do? - The question is what we gonna do.
没人知道都有谁被瓦伦丁收买了
God knows who's in Valentine's pocket and who's not.
我们没有选择
We've no choice.
得靠我们自己解决
We are gonna have to deal with this ourselves.
跟我来
Follow me.
-这是什么鬼 -我不知道
- The fuck is this? - I have no idea.
你们在摆弄的是
What you're playing with...
一个单人跨大气层的原型机
is a prototype personal trans-atmospheric vehicle.
是根据里根的星球大战计划发明的
It was developed as part of Reagan's Star Wars project.
虽然看起来很原始 但应该还是可以用的
Its pretty basic, but it should still work.
我们要把瓦伦丁的一个卫星给打下来
We're going to take out one of Valentine's satellites.
中断链接 停止信号的发送
We're gonna break the chain. Stop the signal.
这样便会让他花几个小时来重新启动
It will take him a couple of hours to reboot it.
能给我们争取足够的时间
Which buys us enough time
让我黑进瓦伦丁的主机
for you to get me into Valentine's mainframe...
然后就能关掉它了
so I can shut it down.
兰斯洛特 你来使用这个 穿上你的宇航服
Lancelot, you are going to be using it. Get into your halo suit.
瑞典首相请求降落许可
The Swedish Prime Minister requesting permission to land.
允许降落
Permission granted.
-请 -谢谢
- Please. - Thank you.
我们还会等来多少人
- So how many more are we expecting?
没多少了 大部分人都有自己的地堡
- Not many. Most have their own bunkers.
我想来这里的都是紧张过度的人
I figure we're just getting really nervous ones.
欢迎你 首相先生
Welcome, Prime Minister.
看来这个植入物能够发射一种反信号
It seems the implant can emit some kind of counter signal...
来保证这些人
to ensure the wearer remains
不被电话卡发射的电波所影响
unaffected by the waves from the SIM card.
你说的是把所有人都变成杀人狂的那个电波
The waves that turns everyone into a psycho killer?
差不多 但是他们应该没有告诉这些人
Quite. But what they probably didn't tell anyone...
这个小芯片会按照他的指令 瞬间灼伤他们的软组织
Is that it can also super heat their soft tissue at his command.
瓦伦丁只选了一小部分人收到倒计时警告
Valentine's selected his chosen few to get the countdown warning.
他得确保
He had to be sure that it
计划不能外泄
didn't blab it to the wrong people beforehand.
这些对我们有什么帮助
And how does this help us right now?
没有帮助 洛克茜 我们出发吧
It doesn't. Roxy, here we go.
你上升得越高 气球就会膨胀得越大
The higher you go, The more the balloons expand.
当你到达大气层边缘的时候 气球就会爆炸
When you reach the edge of the atmosphere, they will explode.
你得在气球爆炸之前部署好导弹 明白吗
You need to deploy your missile just before that, okay?
大气层的边缘
The edge of the atmosphere.
一旦你部署成功
And once you've deployed,
必须解除装备马上降落
you'll need to release for descent fast.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你能做到的 好吗
You can do this, okay?
艾格西 快点 我们的时间不多了
Eggsy, come on. Time is not our friend.
你要用亚瑟的邀请函混进去
Getting in with Arthur's invitation, you gonna need to blend in.
-我来假扮亚瑟吗 -他的邀请函在他的手机里
- I'm supposed to be Arthur? - His invitation's in his phone.
把电话给他们 然后说出真名 彻斯特·金
Give them this and give his real name: Chester King.
-那你怎么办 -我是飞行员 我就待在这里
- And what about you? - I'm the pilot. I'm gonna stay here.
我穿起来会合身吗
Is that gonna fit me?
定做的衣服永远都会合身的
A bespoke suit always fits.
记得感谢哈利帮你订了一套
Just be grateful Harry had it made for you.
快去换上
Get dressed.
他们怎么了
The fuck's wrong with them?
我不知道 大屠杀之前还有什么事可以做么
I don't know. Could have something to do with mass genocide?
把话筒给我
Give me the mic.
大家听好了
Everybody listen up.
你们他妈到底怎么了
What the fuck wrong with you people?
我要提醒一下你们 今天是一个庆祝的日子
I just want to remind you that today is a day of celebration.
把死亡抛诸脑后
We must put aside all thoughts of death,
重点集中在新生上
and focus on birth.
一个新时代的诞生
The birth of a new age.
我们不必为那些献出生命的人而哀悼
We mustn't mourn those who give their lives today.
我们应该向他们的牺牲致敬
We should honor their sacrifice.
她有我的新号 给我回电话 你会没事的
She got my number, so call me back then you'll be fine.
他们扮演着拯救人类的角色
And their role in saving the human race.
我们必须抛开怀疑和内疚
We must put aside doubts and guilts.
你们是被选中的人
You are the chosen people.
当大人们给孩子讲述
When folks tell their kids
诺亚方舟的故事时 诺亚就是坏人吗
the story of Noah's Ark, is Noah the bad guy?
上帝是坏人吗
Is God the bad guy?
那动物们都成双成对登上方舟也不对吗
How about the animals marching two by two?
当然不是
Of course not.
这就是了 大家不要再愁眉苦脸了
Yes, that's it. So let's turn that frown upside down.
吃好 喝好 尽情享乐吧
Eat, drink and party.
我们在新时代再相见
And I'll see you all in the new age.
洛克茜 是我 上面风景怎么样
Rox, its me. How's the view?
-很可怕 -我这里不错哦
- Hideous. - Mine's pretty sweet.
-他们给你定制了西装吗 -不 还没有
- They made you one of these suits yet? - No, not yet.
至少这是个盼头
That's something to look forward to then.
我们准备进入瓦伦丁的基地了 挂了
We're coming up on Valentine's base. Gotta go.
祝你好运
Good luck.
看起来不错啊 艾格西
Looking good, Eggsy.
感觉也不错 梅林
Feeling good, Merlin.
这里是N247CK号
This is November 2-4-7
请求降落
Charlie Kilo requesting permission to land.
允许降落
Permission is granted.
靠
Fuck me.
艾格西 走吧
Eggsy, We're on.
彻斯特·金
Chester King.
金先生 欢迎您
Mr. King, welcome.
我想你应该了解
I'm sure you've adhered
瓦伦丁先生要求禁止携带武器的规定
to Mr Valentine's strict no weapons policy...
如果您不介意的话
but if you don't object..
-当然不了 -谢谢
- Of course. - Thank you
您有行李吗
Do you have any luggage?
恭喜你 迈克罗夫特
Congratulations, Mycroft.
你从我的飞行员晋升为我的贴身男仆了
You just graduated from my pilot to my valet.
-脸皮真厚 -明白了吗
- Cheeky. - Understood?
很好
Good.
谢谢
Thank you.
艾格西 找一台电脑让我连上网络
Eggsy, find a laptop. Get me online.
时间不多了
The clock is ticking.
要记住 尽量混进去
And remember: Try to blend in.
先生要喝点什么吗
Would sir care for a drink?
马提尼杜 用松子酒
Martini. Gin,
不用伏特加
not vodka, obviously.
加点刚开瓶的苦艾酒
Stirred for 10 seconds while
然后搅拌十秒左右
glancing it an unopened bottle of vermouth.
谢谢
Thank you.
梅林 你能看见这里吗
Merlin, you clock in this?
我看见了 注意力集中
Yes I am. Stay focused.
兰斯洛特 你做的很好 不用再上升了
Lancelot, you're doing great. Not much further to go.
是 梅林
Yes, Merlin.
艾格西 快点让我连上网络
Eggsy, get me online. Now.
好 马上来
Yep. I'm on it.
兰斯洛特 你快达到高度上限了
Lancelot, you're approaching your altitude limit.
那些气球撑不了多久了
These balloons won't last much longer.
准备发射导弹
Start to engage missile.
这个社会没救了 这万寿无疆的社会
The society is dead. Long live society.
你说的没错
Amen to that.
-莫腾·宁德特姆 -切斯特·金
- Morten Lindstrm. - Chester King.
你是怎么连上网的
How'd you get online?
哦 这是个封闭式网络
Oh well, it's a closed network,
你看 有授权才能上网
you see. For authorized connections only.
我已经定位到卫星了
I've got a fix on the satellite.
你的时间准吗
Do you have the correct time?
我想我的表还停留在上一个时区
I think I'm still on my last time zone.
哦 我看看
Oh yeah. Lets see now.
选择模式
系统分析进行中
艾格西 我连上网了 你现在赶快回到飞机上来
Eggsy, I'm in. Get your arse back to the plane now.
马上来
I'm on my way.
兰斯洛特 祝你好运 发射倒计时 三 二
Lancelot, good luck. Firing in three, two...
悠着点
Nice and slow.
你他妈的在这干什么
What the fuck are you doing here?
很明显 我的家族理所当然地被邀请了
Well, my family was naturally invited. Obviously.
现在 你给我慢慢站起来
Now get the fuck up. Slowly.
兰斯洛特 快点发射
Lancelot, hurry up and fire.
另一个气球要爆炸了
The other balloon is gonna blow.
是 梅林 我就快锁定它了 再给我一秒
Yes, Merlin. I've nearly got it. Give me a second.
瓦伦丁 我抓住了个间谍
Valentine, I've caught a fucking spy.
V镜 放大画面
V-Glass, zoom.
是那个男仆小子
It's that young valet.
这狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
搞定了
Got it.
〔目标锁定〕
目标锁定
该死 拉响警报
Oh shit. Sound the alarm.
我不会容许任何差池的
I'm not taking any chances.
你发出最后两分钟的倒计时警告
Okay, you send out two minutes warnings.
我来开始重建系统
I'm starting the override.
倒计时启动
Countdown initiated.
启动飞机升降台
-你看到他了吗 -就在这
- You see him? - Right here.
艾格西 左转 前面有两个守卫
Eggsy, take a left. Two guards up ahead.
兰斯洛特 立马脱离装备
Lancelot, release now.
艾格西 直走再右转 那里还有两个
Eggsy, straight ahead and then right. There's two more.
好极了 大家都站起来吧 为胜利日倒数吧
All right, everybody on your feet. Countdown to V-Day.
欢迎来到新纪元
Welcome into new age.
艾格西 继续左转 进入一条窄道
Eggsy, next left. Got a narrow tunnel.
开始了
Here we go.
十
Ten...
九
Nine...
八
Eight...
七
Seven...
六
Six...
五
Five...
四
Four...
三
Three...
二
Two...
一
One...
生物识别技术授权
系统故障
好极了 你们俩都干得漂亮
Nice. Well done, both of you.
它失灵了
It's not working.
它不应该出问题的啊 他妈的怎么回事
It's supposed to be working. What the fuck?
做的好 洛克茜 好姑娘
Yes, Well done, Rox. Good girl.
我们的一个卫星失联了
We've lost one of our satellites.
系统分析完毕
噢不 这个我可没法黑进去了
Oh no no. There's no way I can hack past that.
发现生物识别技术授权系统
怎么回事
What's going on?
有什么问题吗
Is there a problem?
嘿 你们没必要拿枪 我只是个开飞机的
Come on, there's no need for guns. I'm just a pilot.
该死 梅林
Fuck.. Merlin.
快进来
Get in here.
快点
Come on.
-我们快点离开这鬼地方 -我们走不了
- Let's go the fuck out of here. - We can't.
我进不去瓦伦丁的系统
I can't get into Valentine's machine.
它设置了生物识别系统
It's got biometric security.
你得回到里面去
You're gonna have to get in there
确保他的手再也碰不到他的桌子
and make sure his hand never touches that desk.
你在逗我玩吗
You taking a fucking piss?
恐怕不是
I'm afraid not.
把枪给我
Let's me have that then.
这是我的
This is mine.
我带你去拿你的
I'll show you yours.
选得好
Good choice.
重新连上卫星链要多久
How long to relink the satellite chain?
连接断开
要一个小时 或两小时
It can take an hour. Maybe two.
狗屎 就把这两个拉近不就行了
Bullshit. Just bring these two closer together.
但是这颗卫星不是你的
But that's not yours.
V镜 打给E先生
V-glass, call E-man.
E 我是V 听着 我现在遇上点麻烦
E, its V. Listen man, I got a little hiccup on this end.
我需要你的帮忙
I need a piggyback.
我的一个卫星刚刚被毁了
One of my satellites just
但是你的卫星就在它旁边
went down but is right next to one of yours.
你果然懂我 你搞定这个要多久
You read my mind. How long before you make that happen?
走
Go.
我们马上就能重新联上网了
We should be coming back online.
百分之事十了
10%
艾格西 瓦伦丁用了别人的卫星
Eggsy Valentine using someone else's satellite.
他就快重新连上卫星链了
He's gonna reconnect the chain.
不用多久就能连上了
Its gonna take him no time at all.
已经20%了
Its at 20%.
艾格西 瓦伦丁给你准备了一个惊喜 动作快点
Eggsy, Valentine's got a present for you. Get a move on.
-那个特工小子死了吗 -还没有 不过快了
- Is that Kingsman kid dead yet? - Not yet. But he will be soon.
好极了
Good.
梅林 我被困住了
Merlin, I'm fucked.
我也是
As am I.
他们从两边夹击我 我没路可走了
They're coming at me from both sides. I'm out of options.
洛克茜 帮我个忙
Rox, I need a favor.
打电话给我妈 让她把自己锁起来
Call my mum and tell her to lock herself away from Dean
远离迪恩还有宝宝
and the baby.
还有 告诉她我爱她
And tell her I love her.
梅林 你记得那些你说
Merlin, you remember those
对我们没用的植入芯片吗
implants you said were of no use to us?
你可以激活它们吗
Any chance you could turn them on?
该我表演了 瓦伦丁
My turn to play, Valentine.
噢不 他妈的他在干什么
Oh no. What the fuck is he...
我没法截停
I cant stop this.
安全漏洞
激活安全
植入芯片
是
否
是的 麻烦你了
Yes, please.
安全植入芯片已激活
不
Nooo....
这真是太他妈的壮观了
That was fucking spectacular.
梅林 你真是个天才
Merlin, you're a fucking genius.
外面到底怎么回事
What the fuck is happening out there?
你不是那个失踪的公主吗
Aren't you that princess who went missing?
你能救我出去吗
Can you get me out?
如果我能的话 你会给我一个吻吗
Well if I do, will you give me a kiss?
我一直梦想可以亲吻公主
I've always wanted to kiss a princess.
如果你现在就救我出去
If you get me out right now,
我给你的就不止一个吻那么简单了
I will give you more than just a kiss.
你他妈的混蛋
You motherfucker.
你们真的以为我会傻到
Did you really I was stupid enough
在我自己脑袋里植入那玩意儿吗
to implant one of those things in my own head?
你们都他妈疯了吗
What are you? Fucking crazy?
你们为什么要杀了那些无辜的人
All those innocent people killed and for what?
你们根本没有阻止我
You didn't stop shit.
好了 我锁好门了 你还要我干什么
Fine, I have locked the door. What do you want me to do now?
按我说的 把你的女儿关进厕所
As I said, put your daughter
然后把钥匙扔掉
in the bathroom and throw away the key.
计划仍在进行
It's still happening.
-你疯了吗 -你照做就是了
- You fucking insane? - Just do it.
艾格西 信号发出了
Eggsy, the signal's started.
赶快让瓦伦丁的手离开那该死的桌子
Get Valentine's hand off that bloody desk now.
抱歉 美人 我得去拯救世界了
Sorry, love. Gotta save the world.
如果你拯救了世界 我让你后入我菊花
If you save the world, would you do me in the asshole?
我马上回来
I will be right back.
祝你好运哦
Good luck.
伦敦
London.
里约
Rio.
趴下
Get down.
你做到了
You did it.
这玻璃撑不了多久了
This glass is not gonna hold long.
你待在这里
You stay here.
梅林 快点告诉我怎么上去
- Merlin, quickly how do I get up there?
继续开枪 我在找路线
- Keep shooting. I'm find a route.
明白了
Understood.
我们又连上了
We are back up.
这真是太好了
This is great.
艾格西 快点搞定它
Eggsy, fucking get on with it.
狠狠收拾他 亲爱的
Kick his ass, darling.
首尔 加拉加斯 孟买
Seoul, Caracas, Mumbai.
杀了那臭小子
Kill that motherfucking...
艾格西 整个世界都要崩溃了
Eggsy, the world is going to shit.
-他死了吗 -还没有
- Is he dead yet? - Not yet.
别拿你的脚玩他了 杀了他
Stop playing with your foot. Kill him.
加塞尔
Gazelle.
Gazelle!
快点
Come on.
杀了他
Kill him.
干得漂亮 孩子
Well done son.
太好了
Yes!
太棒了 艾格西
Yes! Eggsy
做得好 艾格西
Well done, Eggsy.
你也是 兰斯洛特
And you, Lancelot.
对不起 妈妈永远不会伤害你的
I am sorry. Mommy would never hurt you.
妈妈永远不会伤害你 对不起
Mommy would never hurt you. I am so sorry.
你没事吧
You okay?
哈利会为你感到骄傲的 艾格西
Harry would be proud of you, Eggsy.
他没看错人
He was right.
怎么了 哥们
What's up man?
到了你说风凉话的部分了吗
Is this the part where you say some really bad pun?
就像你跟哈利说的
Its like you said to Harry:
这可不是那种电影 哥们
This ain't that kind of movie, bro.
太完美了
Perfect.
艾格西 你要去哪
Eggsy, where you going?
你没必要拿香槟 飞机上有很多
There's no need for champagne We have got lots on the plane.
你拯救世界了吗
Did you save the world?
是的 没错
Yes I did.
那么 你要进来吗
So, You gonna come in?
是的 我要
Yes, I am.
梅林 这门锁住了 我怎么进去
Merlin, this cell's locked. How do I get in?
密码是2625
26-25.
梅林 你就是我的秘密武器
Merlin, you're the governor.
你欠我一次 艾格西
You owe me, Eggsy.
艾格西
Eggsy
我的妈呀
Oh my word.
米歇尔 关掉这鬼东西 听得我恶心
Michelle, turn that shit off, its turning me nutty.
但我很喜欢这首歌
I rather like that song.
就让它开着 妈妈
Leave it on eh, Mom.
小混蛋回来了
Mugsy's back.
你终于回来给我个交代了吗 小子
You finally come to have that word with me, have you son?
还是你又要逃走然后装作
Or are you going to run away again and pretend
又要去打扮成这人模鬼样吗
you're getting another coat dress like that?
你说这个吗
You mean this?
不
No.
我认识了一个伙计
I know this bloke who's just
他刚刚接管了萨维尔街上的一家裁缝店
taken over a tailor shop up on Seville Road.
他给了我一份工作 妈妈
He's got me a job, Mom.
还有很丰厚的津贴
Comes with a lot of perks.
包括一栋房子
Including a house.
来和我一起住吧 妈妈
Come and live with me there, Mum.
-跟我走 -你坐下
- Come on. - Sit down, you.
她唯一要去的地方就是
Only place she'll be visiting
去医院探望你 听到了吗
is you in fucking hospital, do you hear?
你就放过他吧 艾格西 快走 求你了
Just leave him alone. Eggsy, go please. Just go away.
好吧
All right
没错 乖乖听你妈咪的话
Yes, just do as mommy says.
你不如叫你的裁缝朋友
Why don't you ask that tailor friend of yours to knock up
给你做一套围裙 会很适合你的
a nice chicken costume, it would suit you ya mug.
我的一个好朋友曾经说过
As a good friend once said:
不知礼
Manners...
无以
maketh...
立也
man.
-迪恩 -闭嘴
- Dean? - Shut the fuck up.
艾格西 我就好好调教一下你的礼数...
Eggsy, I'm gonna shove your manners up your fucking...
所以
So...
我们是要这样子傻站一天
Are we going to stand around here all day,
还是要痛快打一架
or are we going to fight?